★个人制作:LnexplicableIZY.★  ★ 电影交流群 499155500★
“W”是谁？
"W" who?
W.U.R.G 94.9，紧急召集，
WURG 94.9, the Urge,
哈顿菲尔德是摇滚者之家。
Haddonfield's home for rock.
我是威利小子，
I'm Willie the Kid,
而你，你拿我毫...毫无办法。
and there's n-n-nothing you can do about it.
*长夜来临 明月高悬*
* Late one night when the moon was tall *
*物业怪物们都肆意狂欢*
* The midnight monsters had a ball *
*停尸房中起舞到天亮*
* At the county morgue till the break of day *
*你能听见怪物的低语*
* You could hear those monsters say *
-*嘿兄弟* -*嘿兄弟*
-* Hey, boo * -* Hey, boo *
-*你很酷* -*你也不赖*
-* You're cool * -* You're cool *
*在这午夜怪物跳*
* At the Midnight Monsters Hop *
*木乃伊是乐队的主唱*
* The mummy was a-frontin' the band *
*隐形人不停吹着萨克斯*
* On the yakkety sax the Invisible Man *
*僵尸打着巫毒鼓*
* A zombie on the voodoo drum *
*吉他手也是真奇怪*
* And the guitar man was a real weird one *
-*他们怒视着前方* -*怒视着前方*
-* They scowl * -* They scowl *
-*然后他们咆哮* -*他们咆哮*
-* And they howl * -* And howl *
*在午夜怪物跳*
* At the Midnight Monsters Hop *
*就在破晓来临之前*
* Just before the break of day *
*怪物们都急着走*
* The monsters all are on their way *
*回到老墓地的棺材里*
* Back to the coffin in the old graveyard *
*无头骑士骑着他的马*
* The Headless Horseman was a-ridin' hard *
-*他们走了* -*走了*
-* They're gone * -* They're gone *
-*黎明来临* -*黎明来临*
-* Come dawn * -* Come dawn *
*在午夜怪物跳＊
* At the Midnight Monsters Hop. *
科里，你来得太及时了  。
Corey, you're a lifesaver.
嗨。
Hi.
最近过得怎样？快进来。
How've you been? Come on in.
罗杰！保姆来了！
Roger! Corey's here!
抱歉这么晚了，但安德里亚胃病犯了
Sorry this is last-minute, but Andrea got a stomach bug
-她刚刚喊我过来看看 -没事。
-and literally just called me. -Oh, it's okay.
这是罗杰公司举办的万圣节派对
It's Roger's company Halloween party,
我倒不在乎，但是…罗杰！
and I could care less, but... Roger!
虽然院子打理得一塌糊涂 但愿他照顾孩子时能表现好点。
Hope he's better at childcare than he is at yard work.
你知道，也许明年春天，
You know, next spring,
你应该考虑一些常绿植物。
you should consider some perennials.
比如绣球花
Hydrangeas could really
-跟山茱萸配在一起很和谐。为大学攒钱吗？
-balance out that dogwood. -Saving for college?
-你说你要去哪来着？-我申请了几个
-Where did you say you're going? -Oh, I'm applying
不同的工程项目。
to a few different engineering programs.
今年好好攒点钱，明年秋季班就能去了。
Just saving money this year so I can go next fall.
杰里米！，照看你的人来了！
Jeremy, the sitter's here!
杰里米！
Jeremy!
-啊！你！我会抓住你的！
-Ah! You! I'm gonna get you!
我会抓到你的。
I'm gonna get you.
注意坠机！砰！
Crash landing! Kaboom!
哦!
Oh!
你能教我怎么折雷霆轰炸机吗？
Can you show me how to make a Thunder Bomber?
要史上第一棒的。
Number one of all time.
-我爸爸折得最好。-不要感到有压力。
-My dad can do the best. -No pressure.
好，我会试试看的，小家伙。
Yeah, I'll sure give it a shot, little dude.
你会乖乖听科里先生的话吗？
You gonna be good for Mr. Corey?
科里 我能和你聊几句？-当然。
-Corey. Could I talk to you for a sec? -Yeah.
雷霆轰炸机来了!
Here comes the Thunder Bomber!
我去把糖果放在门口走廊上。
I'm gonna put the candy on the porch.
来要糖的小孩子可以自己拿。
Trick-or-treat kids can help themselves.
冰箱里的东西都可以随便拿。
Help yourself to anything in the fridge.
她做了西葫芦面包。挺好吃的。
She made zucchini bread. It's actually good.
-你有我手机号码。
-You have my number.
-嗯。-如果有急事就打给我
-Okay. -If there's an emergency,
但我们其实就在街尾那边。
but we'll just be right down the street.
坠机了！
Crash!
我还得再叮嘱你一句。
And there is one thing I need to tell you.
自从上个万圣节，迈克尔·迈尔斯做的那些事，
Since last Halloween-- all the events and,
你知道，还有那些报道
you know, the headlines of Michael Myers--
杰里米很怕黑。
Jeremy's been afraid of the dark.
他晚上会尿床。
He's been wetting the bed at night.
所以，额，他还挺难入眠的
And, um, bedtime has been difficult.
我能听见你们说话！
I can hear you!
我可以给他读点睡前故事啥的。
Uh, I can read him a story or something.
他有什么喜欢的书吗？-然后等他睡觉了
-Does he have a favorite book? -Then once he goes to bed,
他会说梦话。
he talks in his sleep.
他说他能听到某种声音。
Says he hears voices.
他只是对那些让他做噩梦的事
He's just really sensitive to things
特别敏感。-好吧，这些听起来
-that give him bad dreams. -Right. All that just sounds
就像是小孩子自己胡思乱想的玩意，对吧？
like normal kid imagination stuff, right?
不要看电视，不要给他吃糖。
-No TV and no more candy.
你们可以玩到八点半或八点四十五的样子。
You guys can play till 8:30, 8:45.
然后他就该上床睡觉了。
Then he should go to bed.
这钱好赚。-是的。
-Easy money. -Yes.
你要不要跟我一起玩？
Gonna come play with me or what?
-这听起来像是在威胁我。
-That sounds like a threat.
万圣节嘛。
It's Halloween.
今晚我们会玩得很开心的。
We're gonna have a good time tonight.
哦。
Oh.
听着，伙计，如果你
Look, man, we can
害怕看怪兽电影，我们可以关掉不看。
shut it off if you're scared of monster movies.
我才不 害怕的是你。
No. No. You're scared.
我都21岁了。我可不怕。
I'm 21 years old. I don't get scared.
你害怕 因为你知道迈克尔·迈尔斯...
You're scared because you know Michael Myers is...
还逍遥法外
恶魔人要来抓你了哦。
Boogeyman's gonna get you.
他抓不到我的。
He's not gonna get me.
迈克尔·迈尔斯只杀保姆，不杀孩子。
Michael Myers kills babysitters, not kids.
好了，这画面也挺恶心的
Okay, that's actually pretty disgusting
小孩不该看这些。
and probably not appropriate for kids.
要不我们还是把电视关了 然后…
Why don't we shut this off, and...
上床前可以玩玩捉迷藏。
we can play hide-and-seek before bed.
你爸妈就快回家了…
Your parents are gonna be home soon and...
我才不想玩捉迷藏。
I don't want to play no hide-and-seek.
太蠢了。我想继续看这部电影。
It's stupid. I want to watch this movie.
我也不想和一个丑不拉几的男保姆
And I don't really feel like pretending to be best friends 。
装作是好朋友
with an ugly-ass boy babysitter.
好吧，再看五分钟，然后你就得上床了。
Okay, five minutes, and then you're going to bed.
你这保姆真差劲。
You suck at babysitting.
我又不是保姆。
I'm not a babysitter.
杰里米！
Jeremy!
关掉电影！
Turn that movie off!
杰里米？
Jeremy?
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
杰里米？
Jeremy?
杰里米！
Jeremy!
杰里米？
Jeremy?
快出来，不管你在哪里，快出来吧。
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
这不好玩，杰里米。
This isn't funny, Jeremy.
杰里米！
Jeremy!
杰里米？
Jeremy?
快救我！科里，救我！
Help! Corey, help!
杰里米？
Jeremy?
他会抓到你的！
He's gonna get you!
他会趁你不备时抓到你的。
He's gonna get you when you least expect it.
-你是不是该睡觉了，科里？-别闹了,杰里米…
Is it your bedtime, Corey? -Okay, Jeremy...
“不管你在哪，你快出来吧，出来吧。”
"Come out, come out, wherever you are."
你赢了兄弟，别闹了，放我出来
You got me, buddy. Okay, let me out.
你怕了吗？-开门好吗？
Are you scared? -Okay?
“我都21岁了。我才不怕。”
"I'm 21. I'm not scared."
杰里米，快开门，放我出去！
Jeremy, let me out. Let me out!
你个小杂种！快放我出去！
You little shit! Let me out of here!
迈克尔·迈尔斯。
Michael Myers.
-杰里米，这不好玩，别闹了好吗？
-Jeremy, it's not funny, okay?
你会给咱俩都惹上麻烦的。
you're gonna get us both in trouble.
放我出去！放我出去！放我出去！快放我出去！
Let me out! Let me out! Let me out! Let me out!
小杂种！
You little shit!
我会杀了你的，杰里米！
-I'm gonna kill you, Jeremy!
这是怎么回事？
What was that?
杰里米！
Jeremy!
-哦,不！哦,天呐！拜托！-杰里米！
-Oh, no! Oh, God! Please! -Jeremy!
-哦,不。哦,天呐。-杰里米!
-Oh, no. Oh, God. - Jeremy!
天呐！杰里米！
Oh, my God! Jeremy!
-杰里米。杰里米!
-Jeremy. -Jeremy!
天呐，不要啊！
God, please, no!
你都干了些什么？
What have you done?
哈顿菲尔德是一座祥和的小镇。
Haddonfield was a peaceful town.
但在许多年前的一个万圣节夜晚，
And then one Halloween night many years ago,
这片祥和就此打破。
all of that was lost.
迈克尔·迈尔斯是邪恶得到化身。
Michael Myers was pure evil.
他夺走了我们的梦想
He took our dreams
将其化为梦魇。
and turned them into nightmares.
在他身陷牢狱时…
As he was locked away in his prison...
...我也隐归他处。
...I disappeared into mine.
之后，正如我所料，
And then, as I predicted,
40年后，他成功越狱
40 years later, he escaped,
哈顿菲尔德不得不再一次对抗
and Haddonfield was once again forced to confront
这个戴着面具的恶魔。
this man in a mask.
他冷血无情地摧残了我的社区...
His senseless brutality ravaged my community...
...还杀了我的女儿。
...and killed my daughter.
在那之后 他便查无踪迹了。
And then he vanished.
觉得不可能吗？
Impossible?
或许如此。
Perhaps.
当人们找寻其杀人动机和意义时
Truth would evolve into legend
真相往往逐渐变为传说，
as people searched for motive and meaning,
人们只得在阴暗之中找寻恶魔人的踪影。
looking in the shadows for their boogeyman.
这是场意外。
It was an accident.
在接下来的几年里，
In the years that followed,
悲痛，责备，猜疑如瘟疫一般席卷登菲尔德，让镇里居民人心惶惶。
the people of Haddonfield descended into a plague  of grief, of blame, of paranoia.
你觉得他还会回来吗?
Do you think he's come back?
迈克尔从不用枪。
Michael doesn't use guns.
迈克尔造成的苦难
The suffering Michael caused
哪怕是从未招惹过他的人
became an infection passing on to people
都会闻之色变
who never even crossed his path.
当小镇自顾不暇时，
And as the town turned in on itself,
我暗自发誓不再屈从于恐惧。
I made a promise not to let fear rule my life anymore.
我购置了一处房产。
I bought a home.
搭筑起充满爱与信任的家。
A place to live with love and trust.
这里既不是陷阱。
Not a trap.
更不是藏身之所。
Not a place to hide.
嘿。
Hey.
自我上次见那恶魔起，已经过去四年了
It has been four years, since I last saw my monster.
如今我在这里，以幸存者的身份分享我的经历
So here I am, a survivor attempting to share my story
并寻得慰藉。
and find healing.
迈克尔·迈尔斯就是恶魔的化身。
Michael Myers was the personification of evil.
这是他们的。
It's theirs.
这是他们的婚戒。
It's their wedding rings.
一切都取决于我们
It's up to each of us
无论是现在锁上门
whether or not we lock the door
去找解决对策…
and find our resolve...
...还是让他进门。
...or let him inside.
让“它”进门。
Let it inside.
让恶魔…
Let evil...
进门。
inside.
艾莉森！该死的！
Allyson! Darn it!
-亲爱的，非常抱歉！-那是什么声音？
-Honey, I'm so sorry! -What is it?
哦,该死！
Oh, fuck!
呃，是我做的派。我把派放进烤箱了。
Um, it's my pie. I put a pie in the oven.
哦,该死！
Oh, shit!
我肯定是忘记定时了。
Oh, I must have forgotten to set the timer.
真该死！
Damn it!
该死！不，不，不，不，哦，不。
Darn it! No, no, no, no, Oh, no.
我可以从商店买一个派回来。
I can get a pie from the store.
不行！我想亲手给你烤个南瓜派。
No! I wanted to bake you a pumpkin pie.
这是万圣节的传统。
It's a Halloween tradition.
-你是不是… -我得走了。
-Are you... -I got to go.
-上班要迟到了。-好吧。
-I'm late for work. -Okay.
你带了去派对要穿的服装没？
But do you have your costume for the party?
我告诉过你，我自己一个人的话就不去了。
I told you, I don't want to go alone.
所以我不去了。
So I'm not going.
哦。
Oh.
这里是W.U.R.G 94.9
WURG 94.9.
现在为您带来威利小子的【冲动】。
Giving you the Urge, with Willie the Kid.
哈顿菲尔德是摇滚之家。
Haddonfield's home for rock.
还有四天就是万圣节了。
It is four days until Halloween.
-你能相信吗？
-Can you believe it?
是时候锁好你的门，拿起刀准备战斗了。
It's time to lock your doors, grab your knife for the fight.
准备好了吗？要是恶魔人
You ready? You ready in case
决定出来寻欢作恶 你准备好了吗？
the Boogeyman decides to come out and play?
反正我准备好了。
I know I am.
不过我们得先谈谈迈克尔·迈尔斯。
But let's talk about that Michael Myers for a minute.
这个人是怎么中枪，中刀的
How does one man get shot at, stabbed up
摔落街头后 还能卷土重来
and then he fall down the street and get back up
让哈顿菲尔德内每个人都闻风丧胆呢？
to scare the piss out of everybody in Haddonfield?
让我来为你揭晓答案--‘因为它根本不是人’。
Let me tell you how-- 'cause this isn't a man'.
它远超与人。他就是一头野兽。
This is more than a man. This is a beast.
一头不会流血的野兽…
One that doesn't bleed...
我很确定变更订单里写了。
I'm pretty sure that was in the change order.
稍等一下，香农。
Hold-hold on a second, Shannon.
嘿，科里，你迟到了！
Hey, Corey, you're late!
你又迟到了！
You're late again!
已经四年了。
It's been four years.
你们又在哪里？
Where y'all at?
是不是在为这个大日子做准备
Training for the big day, perhaps?
打起十二分精神？
Getting yourself in the spirit?
恶魔人只不过还在蛰伏中，
This Boogeyman been sitting in hibernation,
相信我，他会回来的。
but trust me, y'all, he'll be back.
我是威利小子，无限恐怖尽在
I'm Willie the Kid, and I'll be creeping it real
W.U.R.G电台94.9频道…
on 94.9 WUR...
科里，有空来一下吗?
Corey, you got a second?
你觉得怎么样？
What do you think?
还行。
Yeah.
给它上个牌照。
Get it registered.
换点新零件。
Get some new plates.
-我已经不需要它了。-你是认真的吗？
-I got no use for it no more. -Are you serious?
有这么好的引擎带着你，
With a good engine pushing you,
你就能按时上班了，你你懂我意思吧？
finally make it to work on time, you know what I mean?
它还能开动吗？
Does it work?
能啊，就是状态烂了些。
Yeah, it works, just kind of shitty.
嘿，罗纳德？
Hey, uh, Ronald?
谢了。
Thanks.
不客气，孩子。
No problem, kid.
你被捕了。
You're under arrest.
你是我见过最漂亮的女孩。
For being the prettiest girl I know.
谢谢你,道格。
That's nice, Doug.
这就是你让我靠边停的原因吗？
Is that why you pulled me over?
不是。我叫你停车是因为我想你了。
No. I pulled you over 'cause I miss you.
你想我吗？
You miss me?
开个玩笑。
Just kidding.
让你停车是因为
Pulled you over 'cause it looks like
你车上的消音器看起来快掉了
your muffler's about to fall off.
你最好去修一下
Better get that fixed before you have a bigger
-免得以后碰到更大的麻烦
-problem on your hands.
* 海中的怪物啊*
* Oilliphéist in the sea *
*将我的手钉在门上*
* Nail my hands to the door *
*让我双膝跪在地上*
* And my knees to the floor *
*让水别再上涨*
* Stop the water climbing *
*快快停船上岸*
* Get to the shore *
*船上破了个大洞*
* There's a hole in the boat *
*就要沉没啦*
* And it won't stay afloat *
*海怪啊... *
* Oilliphéist... *
你到底要不要买东西啊？
You gonna buy something or what?
本来可以让我开过来的。
I could've drove here.
放松点。我是代驾司机。
Chill. I'm the designated driver.
-我会开车。-拜托别搞坏我的车好吧。
-I know how to drive. -Don't mess up my car, please.
-我不会弄坏你的车的。-好吗？
-I'm not gonna mess up your car. -All right?
-别搞坏了。-放松。
-Don't mess it up. -Chill.
-他爸有点……-我有驾照的。
-His dad is... -I got my license.
别抱怨了。拜托。
It's no hating on. Come on.
比利。你身份证呢？咱们怎么安排？
Billy. I.D.? -STACY: So what's the plan?
-身份证给我 -身份证？
-Give me the I.D. -I.D.?
-是的。-我身份证上周被没收了。
-Yeah. -It got confiscated last week.
我跟你讲过了。-她带了钱。
-I told you. -She's got the money.
-你没带身份证吗？-什么。你没带吗？
-You don't have your I.D.? -Wait. You what?
-等下。等等。嘿, -我身份证没了。
-Wait. Hold on. Hey, yo! -I lost it.
等下。这位新朋友。
Wait.  New friend.
怎么着，你喝牛奶呢。
What, drinking a little milk.
-对。对。-我也喜欢喝牛奶。
-Yeah. Yeah. -I like milk, too.
-听着，是这么回事，老兄。
-Look, here's the deal, man.
我们是高中生
We're seniors, okay?
我们为了这场演出 练习了一整年了。
We've been practicing for our show the whole year, you know.
就为了给今晚的活动做足准备
Loading up for, uh, tonight's game and--
我们是军乐队的。
Well, we're in the fucking marching band.
就是希望 你能做个酷一点的新朋友
We were just hoping you could be a cool new friend, you know.
帮我们买点酒呗。
Just buy us a couple of six-packs.
就帮我和我朋友们一把。好不好，老兄。
Just-just for me and my crew. Come on, man.
不行。
Uh, no.
不行吗？
No?
你是说“不 谢了”那种不吗？
No-no, thank you? What?
-不,我不能。-等下。
-No, I can't. -Oh, wait.
-我知道你是谁。-你做了很糟糕的事。
-I know who you are. -You did something messy.
-真不敢相信他们居然放你出来了。-他是谁啊？
-I can't believe they let you off. -Well, who is he?
-哦,对啊。-没错。
-Oh, yeah. -Yeah.
你就是那个疯子保姆。
You're that psycho babysitter.
他杀了那个孩子，是不是？
He killed that kid, didn't he?
-没错。-有胆杀孩子
-Yep. -Killed a kid and too pussy
-却没胆帮我们买酒吗？-伙伴们
-to buy us some fucking beer? - Guys, you know what?
要不咱们还是算了吧。
Let's just fucking forget about it.
就直接去参加活动吧，好吗？
Let's just go to the game, okay?
-你就是个可悲的恋童癖。-看看他。
-You're just a little pedo. -Look at him.
-让他知道知道厉害，泰瑞。-你算个什么东西？
-Let him know, Terry. -That what you are?
不他妈就是一个小变态 恋童癖吗?
A little fucking pedo creep?
-没错。给他点颜色看看，泰瑞。
-That's right. -Get in his face, Terry.
你算个什么变态小子啊？
What kind of fucked-up kid are you?
-说得对。-没错。-你接下来准备杀谁啊？
-That's right. -Right. -So where's your next victim?
-哇哦！-什么鬼？!
-Whoa! -What the fuck?
你在跟我开玩笑吗，老兄?
Are you kidding me, man?
-该死。
- Oh, shit.
-看看你。-什么鬼啊，泰瑞？
-Look at you. -What the fuck, Terry?
把牛奶洒了一地。
Got fucking milk everywhere.
- 该死。- 看看你干了什么。
- Holy shit. - Look what you did.
嘿！混蛋！
Hey! Assholes!
住手！
Knock it off!
- 我们什么都没做。- 我们就是聊聊天，女士。
-We're not doing anything. -We're just talking, miss.
- 我们闹着玩呢。- 女士。
-We're messing around. -Ma'am.
- 嘿，伙计们。
-Hey, guys.
瞧一瞧 看一看?
Would you look at this?
一个疯子遇上一个怪胎。
I mean, a psycho meets a freak show.
- 哇。- 简直不敢相信啊。
-Wow. -Can't believe it.
你们俩简直事天作之合的一对。
This is a match made in heaven.
- 嘿,拜托。看着我。- 就先这样吧。
-Hey, come on. Look at me. -Ta-ta for now.
走吧，伙伴们。
Let's go, y'all.
迈克尔·迈尔斯。
Michael Myers.
你是疯子还是怪胎啊？
Are you the psycho or the freak show?
嘿，玛戈，你想去看周六的学校演出吗?
Hey, Margo, do you want to go to the school play on Saturday?
- 当然 泰瑞。- 玩得开心啊。
-Yeah, sure, Terry. -Have fun.
你想亲自动手 还是让我来？
So, do you want to do it, or you want me to?
你看看
Look at it.
你在开玩笑吗？
Are you kidding?
你戴起来超级好看的。
It looks great on you.
我知道，但我不准备去啊。
I'm sure it does, but I'm not going.
把整套都穿上，你肯定喜欢。
Once you put the whole outfit on, you'll love it.
要我说啊 无性感不万圣
I say if it's not sexy, it's not Halloween.
看起来某个人已经准备好要过节啦
Well, someone's getting into the spirit of things.
这位先生刚刚出了点意外 需要包扎一下
This gentleman had an accident and needs a little fix-up.
你的伤口有点发炎
You have significant inflammation.
我会问轻一些 给你伤口打点麻药
Um, I'm gonna be nice and numb it here
我的助手就能好好给你清理
so my assistant can clean it up really well,
然后再回来 把伤口缝合起来
and then I will get back and close it with a suture.
你可能会感觉有点刺痛
You're gonna feel a little bit of a pinch here.
好看吧？
Cute, isn't she?
我没有...啊
I don't-- Ow!
不好意思 不好意思
Sorry. Sorry.
- 我很抱歉 太对不起了 - 艾莉森，你在搞什么鬼？
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry. -Allyson, what are you doing?
-是我的错。对不起 - 艾莉森
- It's my fault. Sorry. -Allyson!
- 别 - 对不起 对不起。
-No.  -Sorry, sorry.
不 不 是我的错 是我的问题
No. No, my fault. It was my fault.
-我很抱歉 天啊 - 乱七八糟的
-I-I'm so sorry. Oh, geez. - What a mess.
赶快收拾干净 拿一套无菌工具来
Just clean it up and get a goddamn sterile kit.
然后给他打一针破伤风
And give him a tetanus shot.
我过会再来
I'll be back.
你不能让他这么跟你说话
You shouldn't let that guy talk to you like that.
即使你自己不这么觉得 但这会让你很难受的
It's gonna make you sad, even if you don't think it does.
我曾和更过分的人相处过
I've dealt with much worse.
但是多谢你了
But thank you.
不过 我已经习惯了
Anyway, I've just been dealing with it.
而且我应该要升职了
Well, I'm supposed to get this promotion.
- 但不管怎样，这… - 这么做值得吗？
-But either way, it's just... -Is it worth it?
你做什么了？
What'd you do?
- 呃… - 你的手怎么了？
-Uh... -To your hand?
我本来再上班 然后发生了点小意外
Uh, I was at work, and then I had a little accident.
-所以你的工作也好不到哪儿去 - 嗯?
-So your job sucks, too. -Hmm?
你在哪工作？你是做什么的？
Where do you work? What do you do?
- 我在汽车修理店上班 - 别动
-Oh, a mechanic shop. -Don't move.
别感染了
Don't want to get infected.
我的车一直发出噪音。
So my car's been rattling.
- 发出噪音？ - 对
-Rattling? -Yeah.
是你车里面的排气系统夹子松了
Uh, it's just your exhaust system clamp's come loose.
很好修 五分钟就能修好
It's an easy fix. It takes like five minutes.
简直是易如反掌
Super cinchy.
你只需要一个千斤顶和两个螺丝
You just need a lift and two screws.
“易如反掌”？
"Cinchy"?
你不用现在就去修的
You don't have to fix it right now.
我没带我的工具 但是…
Yeah, I don't have my stuff, but...
我明天回去店里
I am at the shop tomorrow.
到时候再给你修
I can fix it then.
为什么自行车不能自己立住呢？
Why can't the bicycle stand on its own?
不 它可以
No, no. It can.
它有脚架
It's got a kickstand.
因为自行车太累了
'Cause it was too tired.
有道理
Yeah.
我已经不需要自行车了
Oh, I'm actually getting rid of the bike,
如果你想要 你就拿走吧
so if you want it, you can have it.
我有一辆摩托车。
I got a motorcycle.
- 摩托车？ - 对
-Oh, a motorcycle? -Yeah.
可以教我怎么骑吗？
Teach me to ride it?
可以啊
Yeah.
你背上脏了
You have shit on your back.
我来弄吧
I'll get it.
我们应该出去玩玩 一起做点什么
We should go out sometime and do something.
- 和我吗？ - 和我们两个
-With me? -With both of us.
我是说 我们都得到那儿
I mean, we'd both have to be there.
否则就不好玩了
Otherwise, it wouldn't be a very good time.
你不会想这样的
Yeah, you don't want to do that.
我晚饭要迟到了
Uh, I'm gonna be late for dinner.
不过 谢谢你帮我包扎伤口
But, uh, I appreciate the hand.
已经感觉好多了
It feels better already.
所以你就是故意的
So you did that on purpose.
什么啊？
What?
他受伤了
He was injured,
他需要医护处理 而且麦丝医生
he needed medical attention, and Dr. Mathis
- 是咱们这里最棒的医生 - 你信它吗？
-is the best in town. -Do you believe her?
千万别信她说的话
Do not believe a word she says.
-她满脑子都是心机 - 好吧 好吧 好吧
-You know, she's a strategist. -Fine, fine, fine.
她就是想扮演爱神丘比特
She's just trying to play Cupid.
觉得他很帅 人也很好
Thought he was cute. Seemed nice.
你是准备给他打电话
Are you gonna call him
然后邀请他去她的派对
and invite him to her party,
还是准备一个人去？
or you gonna just go alone?
现在选一张牌。嗯哼。
Now pick a card. Mm-hmm.
不是吧 我选到死亡牌了
Oh, no. I got the death card.
别这么想 塔罗牌里面这可不是死亡
No, that's not bad in tarot.
这意味着一个重要阶段结束
that just means a major phase is ending
和新阶段的到来
and a new one is about to begin.
所以就是说 和你约会的那个警察
So, that pretty much puts a nail in the coffin
要成为过去式了
with that police officer you were dating.
哦 道格
Ugh, Doug.
你需要找个新对象才能走出过去
You know, you need to find someone that can let go.
这个人能让你想宽衣解带
That makes you want to rip off your shirt
展示出你光鲜亮丽的酮体 然后说
and show grief your fucking tits and say,
“让我们开干吧”
"You know what? Let's go."
太好吃了
This is delicious.
科里 你的手感染了吗？
Corey. Is it infected?
你的手感染了吗？ 医生怎么说？
Is your hand infected? What did the doctor say?
他说不会有事的 妈妈
He said it's gonna be fine, Mama.
他说你不用担心
He said that you don't need to worry,
他说这只手会恢复得特别好
and he said it would be terrific is what he said.
如果你不能好好监督他的话
Well, I just might have to send him back to the call center
我就把他送到呼叫中心去给德文打工
to work for DeVon if you can't give him proper supervision.
我又不能时时刻刻盯着他
I can't keep my eyes on every second.
你在干什么？
What the hell are you doing?
你在桌子下面偷偷摸摸跟谁打电话呢？
Who's that calling you under the dinner table?
没谁 妈妈。
it's no one, Mama.
你给谁发消息呢？
Who's that person you're texting?
没谁
It's no one.
藏秘密的孩子是吃不到奶油蛋糕的
Boys who keep secrets don't get custard for dessert.
别告诉她摩托车的事情
Don't tell her about the motorcycle, then.
福特旅行车。
Ford station wagon.
等一下
Hold on one second.
有什么需要帮忙的吗？
Something I can help you with?
科里说我应该把车带来这儿修修
Corey said I should bring it in.
上车
Get on.
好 然后…
Okay, so...
这样
Okay.
右手握的是油门 左手握的是你的前...
Uh, right hand, gas. Left hand is your front...
操了 不好意思
Fuck. Uh, sorry.
右手握的是油门和你的前刹
Right hand is gas, also your front brake.
左手握的是离合
And then left hand is your, uh, clutch.
右脚踩的是后刹
Right foot is your back brake.
左脚换挡
And, uh, left foot is the shifter thingy.
简单吧
Simple.
听起来不简单。
Doesn't sound simple.
哟 科里
Yo, Corey!
帮个忙
Come give us a hand.
- 嘿 罗纳德 - 嘿 泰瑞
-Hey, Ron. -Hey, Terry.
不好意思拿这破事麻烦你
I'm sorry to bother you with this shit.
我的傻儿子 车胎都他妈瘪了 还开了三英里
My goddamn son drove three miles on a fucking flat
就因为他不知道要怎么
'cause he doesn't know how to change a tire
给该死的汽车换轮胎
on a goddamn automobile.
真他妈是个天才
Fucking genius.
嗯…我来吧。
Uh... I got it.
顺便再他妈给车修整修整
Yeah, and fucking smarten up.
我先去给罗纳德搭把手 等会就来处理你车噪音问题
I'm gonna go help Ronald and then fix the rattle.
你车的噪音 你车上的...
Your rattle. Your car's, uh...
我不关心车的噪音 我是来见你的
I don't care about the rattle. I came to see you.
我们会把它修好的
We'll take care of her.
学聪明点 小伙子
Just got to be a little smarter, kid.
三磅牛肩肉 放在最上面一层了
Three pounds of ground chuck, right here on the top.
- 谢谢 - 马上把瘦肉给你拿来
Thank you. -Be right back with the lean.
我的天 弗兰克 你从来不吃蔬菜的吗？
Jesus, Frank, have you ever heard of a vegetable?
哇哦 看看谁来了
Well, look who it is.
- 吃点蔬菜对身体有好处 - 我喜欢把
-They're good for you. -Well, I like to
各种肉搅在一起 给加油站的人做可乐饼
mix meats and make croquettes for the guys at the station.
好吧 听起来真恶心
Okay, that just sounds disgusting.
我喜欢你的发型
I like your hair.
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢 我...
Thanks. I, uh...
我有天给他剪短了
I just sort of chopped it one day.
感觉这就像时间一样
It just was-- It felt like time.
哇哦
Wow.
总会有别人来治愈
Somebody else fixed it.
- 挺有用的 - 对
-Help. -Yeah.
你的瘦肉来啦
There goes your lean.
- 谢谢  崔维斯 - 祝你过得开心
-Thank you, Travis. -Have a good day.
-好嘞 - 再见
-Okay. -See ya.
但我跟你说，我感觉重获了新生
But I tell you, I-I feel like I won an extra life.
真的
I really do.
我在当铺给自己买了把吉他
I got myself a guitar at the pawnshop,
最近一直再摆弄它
and I've been fiddling around with that,
我侄女给我下了一个叫罗塞塔石碑的软件
and my niece gave me a Rosetta Stone,
我正在上面学日语
and now I'm learning Japanese.
- 这句是什么意思？ - 意思是我的衬衫丢了
-What does that mean? -It means I lost my shirt.
大概是的 要不就是我的帽子丢了
I think. Or I lost my hat.
我也不确定 我...
I don't know. I...
谢谢
Thanks.
谁知道呢？
who knows?
说不定我还会坐飞机去看樱花
Maybe I'll fly over for the cherry blossoms.
让当地人检验一下我的日语水平
Test it out on the locals.
你现在还在埋头专心写书吗？
You still got your nose in that, uh, book you're writing?
这可是你的问题 你给我出的主意
Your fault. It was your idea.
是吗？
It was?
- 不 我… - 书名起好了吗？
-No, I'm... -Got a title?
我刚刚布置好了办公室
Just set up my office.
我和艾莉森有一栋房子
You know, I have a house with Allyson.
我们住在一起 过得很不错
We're living together. It's nice.
她在跟人谈恋爱
You know, she's been talking to this guy.
你可能认识那个人
You probably know him.
科里·坎宁安
Corey Cunningham.
是 我认识
Oh, yeah. I do know.
他是个好孩子 吃了很多苦
He's a good kid. Had a tough break.
真好 有人在照顾他
It's nice to know somebody's out there looking out for him.
我喜欢你的脸
I like your face.
我是说 见到你脸很高兴
I mean, I like seeing your face.
我也是
So do you.
我的意思是……
I mean...
我也一样 很高兴见到你
I do, too. I like seeing you, too.
你好
Hi.
嘿
Hey.
你在笑什么？
What you smiling about?
你在商店里买了什么？
What did you buy at the store?
- 不好意思？- “不好意思？”
-I'm sorry? -"I'm sorry?"
- 不...不好意思 - 我不明白你的意思
-I'm s-- I'm sorry.  -I don't understand.
你知道他对我姐姐做了什么吗？
Do you see what he did to my sister?
他杀了她的丈夫 还捅了她
He killed her husband, and he stabbed her.
夺走了她的声音
Took her voice!
就因为你 她再也不能说话了
She cannot speak because of you!
你是她的邻居
You were her neighbor,
但是你甚至不知道她的名字 对吧？
and you don't even know her name, do you?
你诱惑了那个男人 还惹恼了他
You tempted and you provoked that man
你就应该离他远远的
when you should've left him alone.
劳里
Laurie.
嘿
Hey.
你还好吗？
You okay?
嗯
Yeah.
我想去看看樱花
I would like to see those cherry blossoms.
我觉得你也会喜欢的
And I think you'd like 'em, too.
哇唔 谁知道该信什么？
Whoo! Who knows what to believe?
我觉得那个1978年从史密斯森林精神病院逃出来的男人
I think the man who escaped Smith's Grove in 1978
不是杀了那些人的凶手
was not the same man who killed all those people.
真正的迈克尔·迈尔斯那天晚上就被杀了
The real Michael Myers was murdered that night,
那个戴着面具的变态
and the heavy breather with the mask was the same man
就是毒死若望·保禄一世的真凶
who poisoned Pope John Paul I.
*我今天毫无魅力 没人想看到我*
* I'm not attractive today, I'm not a sight for sore eyes *
*我不是亚当也不是夏娃 我只是一个焦虑的年轻人*
* I'm not an Adam or Eve, I'm just a nervous young thing... *
- 你在这啊！- 你好
-There you are! -Hi.
我好想你
I thought I missed you.
面具下面的是谁呀？
Who's under the mask?
我是一个稻草人。
I'm a scarecrow.
什么？
What?
我说我是个稻草人
I said I'm a scarecrow.
你很吓人吗？
Are you supposed to be scary?
我一会儿回来
I'll be right there.
我一会儿回来 好吗？
I'll be right back, okay?
我去拿杯喝的
I'm gonna get us a drink.
*花了点时间 但我最终学会了*
* It took a while, but I learned *
*它经历了一个转折 但我转过身来*
* It took a twist, but I turned *
快看
Watch it!
嘿 稻草人
Hey, scarecrow.
喜欢吗？
See anything you like?
嘿 林赛。
Hey, Lindsay.
- 两杯伏特加苏打酒 - 两杯伏特加苏打酒
-Two vodka sodas. -Two vodka sodas.
琳赛 猜猜艾莉森的稻草人是谁
Lindsay, guess who Allyson's scarecrow is.
就是那个睡了疗养院老太太的男的
The guy that fucked the old lady at the nursing home.
小黛 闭嘴
Deb, drop it.
我开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
其实是科里·坎宁安
It's actually Corey Cunningham,
杀了小孩的那个男的
the guy that killed that kid.
别听她瞎说 艾莉森
Don't listen to her, Allyson.
你想和谁在一起都可以
You can be with whoever you want to be with.
没错
Yeah.
那么现在
And right now,
我要和他一起
I'm with him.
嘿 哥们 给我来杯啤酒
Hey, man. Can I get a beer?
嘿
Hey.
你刚刚在那儿跳舞跳得很开心吗？
You're just here dancing and having a good time?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你很抱歉？
You're sorry?
抱歉？ 为杀我儿子抱歉吗？
Sorry? Sorry for killing my son?
我每天早上一睁眼
I wake up every day,
痛苦就向我袭来
and I can't get past the pain.
我难受得不得了 你懂吗？
It kills me. Do you understand?
你觉得你配来这里...
You think you can come here...
不 你根本不懂我的感受 你觉得你能来这里
No, you don't understand if you think you can come here
摘下面具
and take off your little mask
和朋友们大肆玩乐
and have a good time with your friends.
法官可能觉得你是无辜的 但我了解你
A judge might have said you're innocent, but I know you.
我知道这绝不是意外
I know it was no accident.
绝不是意外
It was no accident!
你疯了 所以推了我儿子
You pushed my little boy because you got mad,
你他妈的疯了
and you lost your fucking mind!
无辜的人绝不会那样做 不会
Innocent people don't do that! No!
只有坏人才会
Evil people do.
魔鬼才会
Evil.
科里
Corey!
科里 小心 科里
Corey, watch out! Corey!
科里
Corey!
- 停下 跟我说说话 - 你为什么要带我来酒吧？
-Stop. Talk to me. -Why'd you take me in there?
就是因为这样我才不出门
It's why I don't go out.
- 什么？ 你刚刚…
-What? -You just, you...
把我丢在一大堆人中间 然后...
you threw me in the middle of it, and then you...
你在哪？
Where were you?
我不知道刚刚发生了什么
I didn't know what was happening in there.
我就是想试着 我就是想试着帮你...
I-I was just trying, I was just trying to help you to just...
我他妈不是你的实验品 艾莉森
I'm not your fucking project, Allyson!
我就是...科里 我知道
I just-- Corey, I know!
好吧？我明白那种感觉
Okay? I know what it's like to have
每个人都盯着你 自以为他们了解你
everybody looking at you, thinking that they know you,
明白你经历过什么
thinking that they know what you've been through,
但其实不是
but they don't.
但是那天 我看见你的时候
But when I look at you-- when I saw you the other day,
我只是看见了一个
I just saw a person.
努力想理清这些破事的人
Just a person just trying to figure it the fuck out.
一个想每天起床不再害怕和孤单的人
Trying to wake up every day not scared and alone.
但是 艾莉森 我们俩的不同在于
But the difference, Allyson, between me and you
人们看我好像在想
is that people look at me like,
“这个人是谁？这个怪物是谁？”
"Who is this guy? Who is this monster?"
但他们看到你 会把你当成一个幸存者
And they look at you like-- They see you like a survivor.
你什么意思？
What are you talking about?
我明白了 你从迈克尔·迈尔斯手里逃出来了
I get it. You survived Michael Myers.
你是个勇敢反抗的英雄 但是问问别人
You're a hero with your struggles, and ask anyone.
我是个变态的临时保姆 我是专杀小孩的杀手
I'm the psycho babysitter. I'm the fucking kid killer.
你以为你能拯救我 但你不能
And you think you can fix me, but you can't.
我还是不浪费你的时间了
I'll spare you the heartache.
科里
Corey!
嘿 酷小子 最近怎么样？
Hey, cool kid. What's up?
你要去哪里？
Where you going?
你在这里啊 我一直在找你
There you are, man. I've been looking for you.
- 泰瑞- 我想道歉 好吗?
- Terry. -I want to apologize, okay?
我的老天
Jesus Christ.
你说呢 科里？
So what do you say, Corey? Huh?
这样吧？握个手 交个朋友
How about this? Handshakes and friendship.
别让他等久了 兄弟
Don't leave him hanging, dude.
你怎么总跟这个孩子过不去？
What is your problem with this kid?
- 这人怪坏了我的雷巴戎 - 就是
-This guy fucked up the LeBaron. -Hell yeah.
一元店买的眼镜？
Dollar store designer frames?
哎呀
Oops.
嘿 让我帮帮你 来吧
Hey, let me help you up. Come on.
- 对不起 - 你还好吗？
-Sorry. -Are you okay?
- 哇 哇 - 都他妈的退后
- Whoa. Whoa. - Get the fuck back!
- 嘿 嘿 - 退后
-Hey! Hey! -Get back!
- 退后 - 哇 哇 哇
-Get back! -Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
- 我只是想帮忙 - 退后
- I'm just trying to help. - Get back!
你也要杀了我们吗？就像你杀了那小孩那样？
You gonna murder us? Same way you killed that kid?
你这个小婊子
You little psycho bitch.
你不知道你在说什么
You don't know what you're talking about!
You don't know what you're talking about.
你从头到脚都是个混蛋
You just act like a goddamn asshole
因为你父亲就是这么对你的
because your father treats you like one.
这会传染的 不是吗？
It's contagious, right?
妈的
Shit.
- 你刚才对我说什么？- 没错
-What did you just say to me? -That's right.
我知道被别人讨厌是什么感受
I know what it looks like when somebody hates you.
你爸就他妈的恨你
And your father fucking hates you.
嗯？他恨我？
Hmm? He hates me?
- 比利 - 他恨我 是吗？
-He hates me, huh?
-他很我对吗？ - 嘿
-He hates me, right? -Hey!
比利 停下 比利
Billy, knock it off. Billy!
他恨我？
He hates me?
泰瑞 怎么回事？
Terry, what the fuck?!
哦 该死
Oh, shit!
- 妈的 - 我的老天
- Oh, shit. - Oh, my God.
- 该死 - 泰瑞 你干了什么？
-Oh, shit. -Terry, what did you do?!
- 他摔下去了 - 那个混蛋自找的
-He fell. -Little dick busted it.
- 他死了吗？ - 下去看看
- she dead? - Go down and look.
- 不，你下去看看 - 他妈的
-No, you go down and look. -What the fuck?
我没有推人 他自己摔下去的。
I didn't push nobody. He fell.
- 胡说八道 - 他自己摔下去的？
-Bullshit. -He fell?
是的 就是这样的
Yeah, that's my story.
我们快走吧
Let's get out of here.
到底谁是疯子 泰瑞？ 谁是疯子？
Who's the psycho now, Terry? Who's the psycho?
这个小混蛋活该
Little prick deserved it.
玛戈尔 上车
Get in the car, Margo.
我们杀人了 哥们
We killed a kid, man.
快点
Come on.
嘿 出什么事了？
Hey, what's happening?
我他妈打不开这个玩意儿
Just-- I can't get this fucking thing to turn on.
好了 好了 深呼吸
Okay, okay. Take a breath.
-好的 深吸一口气 - 你就让我发疯吧
-Okay, take a deep breath. -Just let me be mad!
我为什么不能发疯？
Why can't I be mad?!
你可以
You can.
你可以发疯
You can be mad.
你可以尽情发疯
You can be very, very mad
你可以摔东西
and you can smash things.
但是要小心 这样做很容易上瘾的
Just be careful. It's addictive.
你说得对
You were right.
我很喜欢他
I liked him.
嗯
Yeah.
你看到里面那个男人了吗？
You see that man in there?
他时不时地把人带进去
He take people in there now and then.
他为什么没有杀你？
Why'd he let you live?
你马上回去
I say you go back.
回去把面具带给我
You go back in there, and you get me that mask.
我是迈克尔·迈尔斯
I'm Michael Myers.
你他妈的干什么？
The fuck?
小混蛋 他跟你没完了
He not done with you, you little fuck.
嘿
Hey!
你去哪儿了？
Where have you been?
我都要担心死了
I have been worried sick!
科里 我差一点就报警了
Corey, I almost called the missing persons.
你到底怎么回事？
What is going on with you?
科里 我和你说话呢
Corey, I'm talking to you.
她可不是什么好人 该死的
She's no good, damn it.
开门
Open the door.
Open the door!
你要让我担心死吗？
Are you trying to kill me?
科里？ 科里？
Corey? Corey?
不要因为升职的事情难过 好吗？
No hard feelings about the promotion, right?
当然不会 这是你应得的
Course not. You deserve it.
我觉得麦丝医生
I thought for sure Dr. Mathis
肯定会让你当护士长的
was gonna make you the charge nurse.
小黛 我能和你说两句话吗？
Deb, can I speak to you a minute?
小黛 我只说一遍…
Deb, I'm gonna tell you once...
人们叙写自己的故事
People create their own stories
做出他们自己的选择
and make their own choices.
他们只相信他们愿意相信的事情
They believe what they want to believe.
我希望通过我的方式
I'm hopeful, with perspective,
用我的经历慰藉他人
that my experience will help others heal.
你得扪心自问 “我能否自控”
You have to ask yourself, "Am I in control,
“还是被环境所控制？”
"or do the elements control me?"
“生还是死“
"Life or death."
”自杀还是像樱花一样盛开“
"Suicide or cherry blossoms."
你好
Hi.
抱歉 我不是故意要吓你的
Sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
我在等艾莉森
I'm just waiting for Allyson.
科里？
Corey?
没事吧？
Everything okay?
我昨晚在回家的时候被偷袭了
I got jumped on the way home last night.
那些人…
These guys...
那些加油站的孩子在找我茬
Those kids from the gas station that were messing with me
我努力反抗 但是他们…
I tried to stand up for myself, and they, um...
我很抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry.
我来找你 因为我想和你谈谈
I just came 'cause I wanted to talk to you.
我想说我很抱歉，还有…
I wanted to say that I'm sorry and there's...
我不想找借口
no excuse.
但是拜托 拜托你
But if you could, please, if you could just
和我谈谈
take a walk with me.
好吗？
Please?
我杀人了
I killed someone.
我们当时在做纸飞机
We were making paper planes,
可他想看怪兽电影
but he wanted to watch a monster movie.
然后都是一瞬间的事
Everything happened so fast.
我那晚只是希望我们能好好玩
I just wanted it to be a fun night.
享受美好时光…仅此而已
That's all, just... a good night.
但是后来全都失控了
And then it all went bad.
我听说过是怎么回事
I heard what happened.
我知道这听起来很不可思议 但是当…
I know it sounds crazy, but when...
可是人们谈起这件事的时候 我感觉我好像认识你
people would talk about it, it was like I knew you.
好像我一直在寻找你
Like I was looking for you.
然后她带你来到了我身边
And then she brought you to me.
他做错了什么吗？
Has he done something bad?
我不明白你为什么来这里
I don't understand why you're here.
不是 他在和我孙女约会
No, no. He's seeing my granddaughter.
其实是我介绍他们认识的
I introduced them, actually.
你孙女和科里这样的男孩子在一起
Your granddaughter should be so lucky
真是太幸运了
as to be with a boy like Corey.
他很帅 也很善解人意
He's handsome. He's sensitive.
我不太喜欢他和女孩在外面过夜
I don't like it when he stays out
但是他已经长大了
all night with girls, but he's grown.
他可以做自己想做的事了
He can do what he wants.
是的
Yes.
我知道他有自己的难处
I know he's had his difficulties.
我儿子
My son.
在杰里米·艾伦出事之后 整个镇子都针对他
This town turned against him after the accident with Jeremy Allen.
他们本应该同情他
They would've felt for him.
帮助他走出阴影
They would've helped him heal.
可你的恶魔人消失了
But because your boogeyman disappeared,
所以他们需要一个新的怪物
they needed a new one.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我父母被杀以后
After my mom and dad were killed,
我想把一切都一把火烧了
I just wanted to burn it all to the ground
- 离开哈顿菲尔德 - 为什么不离开呢？
-and get away from Haddonfield. -Why not leave?
为什么要留下来？
Why stay?
这个地方有我所有的记忆
All my memories are here.
我觉得你父母都被杀后
I think both your parents got killed
你外婆因此感到内疚
and your grandma feels guilty about it,
所以她把你当成了她的孩子
so she's making you her child.
你应该看看她治疗前是什么样子
If you could've seen her before therapy,
她现在已经好很多了 而我…
sobering up, and me...
我只是不敢想象 如果我走后
I'm just terrified to think what would happen
只剩她孤身一人 会发生什么事
if she were all alone if I left.
所以 你是说 你得一直留在这
So, what, you got to stay here, protect her
保护她？
from herself forever?
听着…
Look...
对不起 我在聚会上昏头了
I'm sorry I lost my head at the party
我一走了之
and I walked away.
那是我的错
That was a mistake.
当时我看着你时 我…
When I look at you, I...
我知道我可以告诉你真相
I know I can tell you the truth.
我不怕这些人了
I'm not afraid of these people.
再也不怕了
I'm not afraid anymore.
告诉我 你想要把房子付之一炬
You tell me that you want to burn it down,
还是想把它烧个干净
or you tell me you want to burn it to the ground.
嘿 一周里碰到两次
Hey. Twice in one week.
太酷了 难以置信
Pretty cool. Hot diggity.
嘿 你之前说你...会打给我
Hey, you said you, uh... you were gonna call.
你说…你会打给我 但你没有打
You were... you were gonna call, but you didn't call.
对 我还没有打给你
No, I owe you a call.
我……我做错什么了 还是...
Did I... did I do something wrong or...
我有约了
I'm with someone.
哦 哦
Oh. Oh.
哦 真对不起
Oops. Uh, sorry for that.
很抱歉打扰你们
I'm sorry for the intrusion.
好吧 呃 今天...是乔·格里洛的...
Well, um, you know, it's, uh... it's Joe Grillo's, uh...
嘿 乔 嘿
Hey, Joe! Hey.
今天是乔·格里洛的生日
Joe Grillo's birthday today.
乔·罗斯做了个海绵蛋糕
And Joe Ross, uh, he made a sponge cake.
你们俩结束后
You two want to stop by, get a slice
-可以来尝尝 - 我们不用了
-after whatever you guys are doing? -We're good.
好吧 你们不想吃
Oh. Okay, you're good.
听我说 就是…
Let me tell you, it's, uh...
如果你改变主意了，还有…
If you change your mind, there's...
她说了我们不用了
She said we're good!
嘿 哥们 你有意见？
Hey, buddy, you got a problem?
我没有
We're good.
哦 该死
Oh, shit.
埃里森
Allyson.
所以你晚上睡不着
So you call Mr. Aggravated Manslaughter
就打给了暴虐杀人狂先生？
at night when you can't sleep?
当你在噩梦看见了恶魔人后
When you see the Boogeyman in your nightmares?
你还觉得跟这个家伙在一起更有安全感？
You feel safe with this guy?
嘿 哥们
Hey, man.
随便说说罢了
Messing around.
埃里森
Allyson.
不 不 不
Nah, nah, nah.
-神经病 - 你没事吧 慕兰尼？
-Psycho. -You good, Mulaney?
没事 我很好
It's all good. It's all good.
需要我们教训某人吗？
We need to go kick somebody's ass?
不 不用 我搞得定
No, no. I got this.
我只是想烧个干净
Just burn it all to the ground.
我来帮你点火
I'll light the match.
想进来坐坐吗？
Do you want to come in?
改天吧
Another night.
啊 操
Ah, fuck!
嘿
Hey!
别惹道格·慕兰尼
You don't fuck with Doug Mulaney!
你在哪？嗯？
Where are you? Huh?
你还说这是个事故
You say it was an accident.
但我知道你做了什么
But I know what you did.
我要打爆你的脸 你这混蛋
I'm gonna fuck your face up, you little shit.
那他妈的是什么？
The fuck is that?
来啊
Help.
给我看看你的能耐
Show me how to do it.
起来 起来 起来呀
Get up, get up, get up.
快起来
Get up!
是谁呀？
Who is it?
是我。
It's me.
天呐 你没事吧？
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
我不知道我怎么了
I don't know what's happening to me.
发生了什么事？
What's going on?
看着我
Look at me.
谁伤的你？
Who did this to you?
嘿
Hey.
看着我
Look at me.
迈克尔·迈尔斯没杀你？
Did Michael Myers let you live?
还是你逃出来了？
Or did you escape?
疼吗？
Does it hurt?
不 不疼
No. No.
我妈妈救了我
My mother saved me.
你俩睡了 对吗？
You're fucking him, aren't you?
这种程度上算是哈登菲尔德的完美故事了
It's, like, the perfect story of Haddonfield in a way.
年轻貌美的女孩爱上了本地的怪胎
Cute young girl falls for local creep.
想象一下 如果你外婆
Imagine if your grandmother had
爱上了迈克尔·迈尔斯
fallen in love with Michael Myers.
但她没有 我听说她用该死的毛衣棒针
But she didn't. I heard she stabbed him
捅进了他的脖子
in the neck with a fucking knitting needle.
你有什么毛病 小黛？
What's your problem, Deb?
你当我不存在似的 对着我说一大通
You talk to me like I'm not even here.
你那张臭嘴一直这么唠叨吗？
Do you ever just shut your goddamn mouth?
我知道 好吗？
I know, right?
我知道我话多
I know I talk too much.
我只是对于恶魔人这档子事很感兴趣
I just get so excited about all that Boogeyman bullshit.
不 我可不认那笔交易
No. I-I'm vetoing that trade.
你的第二接球手在面对马克的最终防守时
Your second receiver for Mark's last-place defense
明显是串通好的
reeks of collusion.
这不是平等的交易
It's not a straight-up swap.
你想带你们团队夺冠吗？
You want to win the championship with class?
别耍小把戏
Stop cheating.
我一直看着他的眼睛
I keep seeing his eyes.
我们在说迈克尔还是这孩子？
Are we talking about Michael or this kid?
科里有着迈克尔的眼神
Michael's eyes in Corey.
我很确定 琳赛
Lindsay, I was so sure.
就跟一开始第一次一样
Just like the first time.
嗨 罗杰
Hey, Roger.
有个人我想让你见见
There's someone I want you to meet.
我一直挺喜欢科里的
I always liked Corey.
有些小孩你一看就知道他们事混球
You know, some kids, you can tell they're a pain in the ass,
但科里是个好孩子
but Corey was a good kid.
我不相信他会做出
And I just couldn't imagine he'd be capable
故意伤人的事
of hurting anyone on purpose.
但经过庭审以后 我...
But with the trial, I...
我脑海里就萦绕着一些念头
just started spinning with theories, and...
最后我想
and eventually I thought,
“放弃它 你永远都不可能解脱
"Give it up. You're never gonna get closure.
没有解脱可言”
There's no such thing."
几年过去了 我时不时遇到他
A couple of years go by, and I'd see him every now and then,
看到大家都躲着他
see the way people avoided him
在他背后做鬼脸
or how they made faces behind his back,
说实话 我很生气
which, if I'm honest, pissed me off.
因为我觉得他们夺走了我的痛苦…
Because I felt like they took my pain...
...我的绝望
...my despair,
把我失去的偷走 变成他们的故事
and they made it about them.
昨天，我在上班的路上
And then, yesterday, I'm on my way to work.
看到他在路上走
There he is.
我想"我得说点什么
And I think, "I'm gonna say something,
证明我老婆是错的
"prove my wife wrong.
想个办法原谅这孩子吧”
Let's find a way to forgive this kid."
于是我在他边上停下车 他看向我
And I pull up next to him, and he looks at me,
但这不是他本人
and it's not him.
至少眼神不像
At least not in the eyes.
我不知道怎么回事
And I don't know, man.
他看得我毛骨悚然
The hairs on the back of my neck stood up.
当时我明白了
Right then, I felt like I got my answer.
杀我儿子的凶手 不是当年那个给我家除草的孩子
The kid who used to mow our lawn didn't kill my son.
我清楚这一点
I know that.
我在路边看到的那个人
But the guy I saw on the side of the road
他已弃明投暗
was down a dark path.
是那场意外之后 镇上的人让他变成这样的
Did the town do this to him after the accident?
还是他的黑暗面一直都在呢？
Or was it always there?
你再给我的笑话捧场呢
You're just laughing at all my jokes,
是吧？
aren't you?
哦 天啊
Oh, my God.
好吧 阿利克
All right, Alexa.
播放罗伯·加尔布雷思的【用你的眼睛告诉我】。
Play "Tell Me With Your Eyes" by Rob Galbraith.
开始播放【用你的眼睛告诉我……】
Here's "Tell Me With Your Eyes..."
你家房子…
This house is so...
可真富丽堂皇
rich.
宝贝 我等了一整天了
Baby, I have been waiting all day for this.
我一直保存着这瓶奥邦没喝
I've been saving this bottle of Au Bon Climat.
你今天上班的时候实在太性感了
You looked so fucking hot at the office today.
介意我去……
Mind if I...
卧室在走廊尽头
Bedroom's down the hall.
去洗个澡
Clean up. Take a shower.
我们卧室见
In fact, I'll meet you in there.
真好 真好
Yes, yes.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
真棒
Yes.
我的天
Holy shit.
这里有医生吗？
Is there a doctor in the house?
好了 宝贝儿
Yeah, baby. All right.
奶酪有了 饼干有了
Got the cheese. We got the crackers.
准备好了
We're ready.
麦丝医生？
Dr. Mathis?
救命 救命 救命 救命
Please, please, please, please.
在那次意外事故以后
After the accident,
我有时候骑自行车过来 坐在楼顶上
I'd ride my bike over here and I'd sit up on this roof.
抬头看着那座塔
And I'd look up at that tower.
想着我能不能爬到塔顶
Wonder if I could climb to the top.
它召唤着我
It was summoning me.
像灯塔一样召唤我回到以前的生活
Like a watchtower or beacon calling me to live my old life.
继续快乐地生活
To be happy again.
我也有那种感觉
I have something like that, too.
它总会给我希望 你知道，事情会
It always gave me hope, you know, things would--
或许一切都能回到
well, maybe somehow things would go back
最初的样子
to the way they used to be.
回到生活翻天覆地之前
Before everything changed.
变得一塌糊涂之前
Infected.
我应该离开所有认识我的人
I got to get away from everybody who knows me.
但是我 我…
But I don't, I...
不想一个人离开
I don't want to go alone.
科里 好了
Corey, come on.
别笑
Stop.
你怕绷带不够
I think you're scared that you don't have enough bandages
不能把我绑住
to keep me together.
科里 你在干什么...？
Corey, what are you...?!
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
你疯了吗？
What, are you insane?
怎么，你想自杀吗？
What, are you trying to kill yourself?
我对永生可没有兴趣
I'm not interested in immortality.
谁在外面搞鬼？
The hell is going on out here?
喂 这是私人领地
Yo, this is private property.
不管你做什么都不安全…
Not safe to be doing whatever the hell you do...
科里·坎宁安
Corey Cunningham.
你在搞什么？ 你个丑瘪三
What you doing out here, you ugly motherfucker?
- 科里 别管他 - 你会吓到孩子们的
-ALLYSON: Corey, stop it. -You gonna scare all the kids.
你别说了
You stop.
我不知道你他妈的跟谁讲话
I don't know who the fuck you talking to,
但我可知道你是谁
but, uh, I know who you are.
没错 我知道劳里·斯特罗德那些事
Yeah, I know the Laurie Strode story.
捉弄一个脑子不正常的人 结果那人成了杀人狂
She teased a man with brain damage, and then he snapped.
你看看你
Look at you.
你也想搞出点名声是吗？
You gonna make a little name for yourself now, huh?
和这个蠢婊子在一起。
Walking around with this dumb bitch right here.
你没有闭嘴的时候
You never shut up.
到处都能听到你的声音
Hear his voice everywhere.
你说得太他妈对了
Oh, you're goddamn right you do.
听威力说话就像听最喜欢的歌
And once Willie get in your ear,
在你脑海里挥之不去。
it's like your favorite song stuck in your head.
给我快滚
Y'all get the hell up off my property
不然我收拾你们
before I fuck y'all up.
好
All right.
你说得对
You're right.
我们走吧
Let's do it.
我不想待在哈顿菲尔德了
I don't want to be in Haddonfield anymore.
我就要和你在一起
I want to be with you.
你身上有那女人的气味
I can smell her on you.
她想把你从我身边抢走 是吧？
She's trying to take you away from me, isn't she?
原来你每晚都是去找她
That's where you go every night.
好吧 你走
Well, I say go.
现在就走
You go right now!
从我家滚出去
Get out of my house!
哦 不 不
Oh, no. No.
希望你幸福
I hope you find love.
埃里森
Allyson?
很高兴见到你
It's nice to see you.
恶魔有两种
You know, there are two kinds of evil.
一种是外界的恶魔
There's the evil that exists as an external force
威胁人们的安全
that threatens the well-being of the tribe.
为了生存 人们要对自己可能受到的伤害
Survival depends on understanding and awareness
有所理解 察觉和畏惧
and fear of physical threat to our daily lives.
另一种恶魔就在我们之中
The other kind of evil lives inside us.
就像疾病或感染
Like a sickness or an infection.
这总恶魔更危险 因为人们可能不知道它的存在
It's more dangerous because we may not know we're infected.
我是坏人吗？
Am I a bad person?
你说吗？
Are you?
呃…
Well...
...我们都是满不在乎的
...we're both fucked-up.
我想帮你 科里
I want to help you, Corey.
让我来帮你
Let me help you.
或者让我找人帮你
Or let me find help for you.
你不能和艾莉森在一起
You can't have her.
她不合适你
Allyson is not equipped for this relationship,
我不会让她受伤的
and I will not let her get hurt.
所以你给我离远点…
So stay the fuck away...
这都是你造成的
You started this!
是你当初接纳我
You brought me in! You invited me!
你才是罪魁祸首
But you're the one to blame.
“你想动手 还是想让我来？”
"You want to do it, or you want me to?"
如果我不能得到艾莉森…
If I can't have her...
其他人也别想
...no one will.
你想帮艾莉森是吗？ 让她自己做主
You want to help Allyson? Let her live her life.
她现在和我在一起了
She has me now.
你放弃吧
You should give in.
你第一次直视他的双眼时
You should surrender to that feeling you had
就不该在内心挣扎
the first time you ever looked into his eyes.
其实你期盼迈克尔回来找你
You secretly hope Michael comes back for you.
我是精神病
I'm the psycho.
你是怪人
You're the freak show.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
我们得走了
We need to leave.
现在不行 我的上班
I can't right now. I'm working.
那就晚上
Tonight, then.
晚上九点见面好吗？
Will you meet me at 9:00?
在七十四号公路的餐厅
At the diner off 74.
我们得谈谈你外婆
We need to talk about your grandmother.
她想杀了我
She wants to kill me.
- 什么？- 你没听错
- What?  - Yeah.
我受不了了
I can't take it anymore.
是时候离开哈顿菲尔德了
It's time to say goodbye to Haddonfield.
我需要你的一样东西
You got something I need.
你只不过戴着一个万圣节面具
You're just a man in a Halloween mask.
我看你还有什么本事
What are you gonna do now?
完事给他打电话
Call him after.
我不想去你家 伙计
I don't want to go to your house, man.
你爸爸总他妈吼我们
Your dad always fucking yells at us.
真他妈遗憾 你家买不起房
Too fucking bad. You should've got your own.
你不应该吃这个
Shouldn't have any of these anyway.
为什么我们不能去她家？ 她家才有钱
Why can't we go to her house? She's the one that's rich.
- 什么？ 哦对 - 这他妈谁干的？
-Oh, what? Yeah. Shoot. - What the fuck?
怎么了？
What?
他死定了 上车
He's dead! Get in!
操 操
Oh, shit. Shit.
找到你要找的额东西了吗？
Did you find what you're looking for?
我猜你打算开启一段美好的旅程
I imagine you're going on a wonderful trip.
- 你打算瞒着我吗？ - 有什么区别吗？
-Were you gonna tell me? -What difference does it make?
区别很大 艾莉森
It makes a big difference, Allyson.
我觉得他不对劲 会伤害到你
I feel he is capable of real harm.
你就担心这个？
Is that what bothers you?
你是怀疑还是妄想？
Is it suspicion or paranoia?
直觉？ 还是有什么头绪？
Intuition? An inkling?
你有头绪吗？
You got an inkling?
我去了他家 见到了他母亲
I went to his home. I met his mother.
我知道 他告诉我了
I know. He told me.
所以 你开始跟踪他了？
So, you're what? You're stalking him now?
- 没有 - 而且你在威胁他
-No. -And you're threatening him.
- 你对他说了什么？ - 我在他眼里看到另一个人
-What did you say to him? -I-I see the same thing in him
- 看到了迈克尔 - 迈克尔。
- that I saw in Michael. - Michael.
你才是迈克尔·迈尔斯
Michael Myers is who you are.
你没明白我的意思 艾莉森
You're not listening to me, Allyson.
我是想保护你
I am trying to protect you.
我不想要你保护
I don't want your protection!
但你...你可以生活的很幸福 艾莉森
But you-you can have a good life, Allyson.
快乐的生活
A good life.
但不要和他在一起
Just not with him.
你假装走出阴影了 但根本就没有
You pretend like you moved on, but it's bullshit.
其实你是对死亡着迷
You're actually just obsessed with death,
你把这一切视为游戏
like it's some sort of game.
不玩完你不会罢休
And you're not gonna rest until you've finished it
或者等所有人都像你一样悲惨 你才会收手
or until everybody else is as fucking miserable as you are!
科里是唯一让我有感觉的人
I need to get out of here before this town kills
在他被这个小镇逼死之前 我一定要离开
the one person that actually makes me feel something.
他已经误入歧途了
He is on a dark path!
我不想让你陷入其中
I'm not gonna let this happen to you!
你必须要相信我
You have to believe me!
相信你？
Believe you?
你想让我相信你？
You want me to believe you?
这些混乱都是你引起的
Because of the hysteria that you caused
就是因为信你 我朋友都死了
when I trusted you, my friends are dead.
我父母也死了
My parents are dead.
你才是一切的罪魁祸首
You're the one that's capable of fucking harm!
你确定他现在在这儿吗？
You sure he turned in here, dude?
是的 他就躲在这儿的
Yeah, it's like his hideout or something.
在这儿工作
It's where he works.
- 工作个鬼哦 - 确实 工作了个鬼
-His work is a dump. -It actually is a dump.
好了将真的 他在哪啊？
Okay, no, but seriously, where is he?
- 看 车还停在那的 - 操 快停车
- There's the bike. - Shit, dude, pull over.
太疯狂了
This is gonna be so crazy.
- 走走走 - 比利 你能快点吗？
- Let's go. -  Billy, can you hurry up?
- 科里 - 别挤我
- Corey! - You're squishing me.
- 老天爷 - 那他去了？
- God.  - Where'd he go?
出来 科里
Come out, Corey!
科里 出来 我还等着回家睡觉呢
Corey, I just want to kiss and make up, my man!
- 出来吧 - 别那么讨人厌
-Come on! -Stop being a punk!
- 科里 - 你在哪儿？
- Corey! - Where you at, man?
你待会就会知道划我老爹的车会怎么样
I'll show you what happens when you mess with my dad's car!
你可以快点吗 兄弟？
Can we hurry this up, man?
等等 我想到了
Oh, I got an idea.
比利 你会车上
Billy, back the car up.
好
Bet.
把这个链子带上 走吧
Grab that chain. Let's go.
泰瑞 办公室里有人
Terry, there's somebody in the office.
别像个胆小鬼一样
Stop being a chickenshit.
把链子固定到轮子上
Run it through the wheel.
一会儿咱们拖着走
We're gonna tie it to the back of the car,
直到这个破车啥也不剩
and then we'll drag it till there's nothing left.
破车
Dusty-ass bike.
操
Shit.
- 快点 比利 比利 - 快点儿 快点啊
- Let's go, Billy. Billy! - Come on, Terry. Hurry up, man.
- 好像有人 - 比利
- Someone's here. - Billy!
快点儿 比利 你还在等什么
Come on, Billy! Let's get this punk!
快点儿
Let's go!
哦 我的天 比利
Oh, my God. Billy.
比利 你在等什么 我操…
Billy, what are you trying to do, man? Suck your own...
哦 我的天
Oh, my God!
他妈的 怎么回事？
What the fuck?
泰瑞？
Terry?
怎么了？
What's wrong?
比利的死了
Billy's dead!
-什么？ - 什么？
- What? - What?
你说什么？
What are you talking about?
哦 该死
Oh, shit.
史黛西？史黛西？
Stacy? Stacy?
…发生什么了？
What... what's happening?!
该死的
Damn it!
史黛西
Stacy!
救命 救命 救命 救命
Help, help, help, help!
救命 救救我 救救我 救救我
Help! You got to help me! Help me!
玛尔戈
Margo!
哦 我的天呐
Oh, my God!
玛尔戈 玛尔戈
Margo! Margo!
你说句话
Speak to me.
你还好吗？ 你还好吗？
Are you okay? Are you okay?
冷静点 我带你走
Stay calm. I'm gonna get you out of here.
别担心 我带你离开
Don't worry. I'm gonna get you out.
你自己平复一下
Try to be calm.
装好弹了
It's loaded.
待在这儿
Stay here.
我不想死
I don't want to die.
- 救救我 救救我 - 嘿 嘿
-Help me! Help me! - Hey, hey!
坚持住 别动
Hold on. Hold on. Hold still.
别动 我把这个先搬开
Hold still! I'll get it off you.
他来了
There he is!
科里？
Corey?
被我逮住了吧
I got you!
-你这个死神经病 被我抓住了吧 - 不 不要
- I got you, you fucking psycho! - No, don't!
史黛西 史黛西
Stacy. Stacy.
天啊
God.
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
- 泰瑞 - 玛尔戈
- Terry. - Margo!
泰瑞
Terry.
天哪 我的老天
God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
史黛西呢？
Where's Stacy?
史黛西已经死了
Stacy's dead.
你也要死了
You're dead, too.
- 什么？- 泰瑞
- What? - Terry.
不
No.
哦 该死
Oh, shit.
你会闻到柠檬皮的味道
It's the zest of a lemon peel.
然后轻轻地扭一下
Gives a little fresh twist.
然后呢 蓝莓这个时候就已经很烫了
So the blueberries, obviously, are really hot.
一切准备就绪之后
And then when it's all ready to go,
我们就把淡奶沙司放进冰箱里冰镇 然后搅拌……
we'll go and freeze the custard and then whip...
罗纳德？
Ronald?
衣服我已经洗干净了
I have laundry.
我是把衣服放衣柜里呢
I can put it in your dresser,
还是就留在篮子里
or I can leave it in this basket here.
……把容器放进冰箱
...this container and put it in the freezer
等待半小时到一个小时
for about, oh, half an hour to an hour
这样就完全凝固了
so it'll firm up.
然后就可以吃了
Now we're gonna eat it.
看起来不错呢
That looks good.
口感有点像冰淇淋 又有点像曲奇…
A little ice cream, a little cookie...
热线已经开通 你随时可以电话咨询
Ooh, the hotline is open, and we are taking requests.
来一首复活之歌
Songs for the resurrection.
释放我们心中的野兽
What's gonna get our monster out?
让我们惊声尖叫
Give us something to scream about?
你好 电话已接通
Caller, you're on the air.
威利 你拿这些悲剧
Willie, you should be
来赚取流量 你的良心不会痛吗
ashamed of yourself exploiting these tragedies.
哈顿菲尔德还有有三个人下落不明
There are three missing people right now in Haddonfield.
先生 当你和怪兽搏斗的时候
"Beware," sir, "that when fighting monsters,
“你也会变成怪兽
"you yourself do not become a monster,
当你凝视深渊的时候
"for when you gaze long into the abyss,
深渊也在凝视你”
the abyss gazes also into you."
尼采还说过呢”没有音乐...“
Nietzsche also said, "Without music..."
＂...生命将是一个错误”
"...life would be a mistake."
你需要帮助吗？
Can I help you?
嘿 你到底是他妈的谁？
Hey, man, who the hell are you?
嘿，搞什么…哦
Hey, what the f... Oh!
艾莉森 我很抱歉
Allyson, I'm sorry.
抱歉我说过难听的话
I'm sorry for what I said.
对不起 求你了
I'm sorry. Please.
我只是想让你回家
And I just want you to come home.
- 911 - 请说
-911. -Yes.
我想报告一起自杀
I would like to report a suicide.
磨坊尽头街1206号
1206 Mill's End Road.
你真的以为我会自杀？
Did you really think I'd kill myself?
我那么努力…
I have tried so hard...
想获得同情心和怜悯
...to have compassion and find mercy.
但又有什么意义呢？
But what's the point?
你是来杀我的 那就动手吧
You came here to kill me, so do it.
我们都最终会
You know, we all learn the truth
看清对方是什么样的人
about each other eventually.
你真的觉得
Did you really think
艾莉森会和你在一起吗？
that Allyson was gonna be with you?
如果我不能拥有她…
If I can't have her...
你个狗娘养的。
You son of a bitch.
你做了什么？
What did you do?
你对他做了什么？
What did you do to him?
不 不
No, no.
不 不啊
No. No.
你为什么要这么做？
Why did you do this?
-不 - 科里 别死 回来
-No. -Corey, come back. Come back.
不 不
No, no.
是你
You!
艾莉森 劳里去哪儿了？
Allyson, where's Laurie?
我们正在处理一通电话 报告了一起自杀案件
We're responding to a call. She called in a suicide.
不
No!
我逃离过你
I've run from you.
也寻找过你
I have chased you.
我曾试着控制你
I have tried to contain you.
也试着原谅你
I have tried to forgive you.
我本以为你是恶魔人
I thought maybe you were the Boogeyman.
但
No.
你只是一个将死之人罢了
You're just a man who's about to stop breathing.
来吧
Do it.
来啊
Do it!
动手吧
Do it.
不
No!
我不会让你经历这样的事的
I'm not gonna let this happen to you.
没关系。
It's okay.
别挡路 就呆在这儿
Get out of the way. Stay here.
别往前
Just stay back.
劳里
Laurie!
迈克尔
Michael.
他死了
He's dead.
还没死透呢
Not dead enough.
我们不该这样
This isn't how we do it.
- 你真是疯了 - 你在干什么？
- You're all crazy. -  What are you doing?
你要带他去哪儿？
Where are you taking him?
哈顿菲尔德是时候从伤痛中走出来了
Time for Haddonfield to start healing.
让大家都看看吧
Let's show them all.
事情不该这样
This is not how it works.
就是今晚
It is tonight.
呃，加强无线电静默。
Uh, stronger on radio silence.
这是新的指令
That's got to be a command.
- 收到 - 收到
-Copy that. - Copy.
走吧
Let's go.
迈克尔·迈尔斯的尸体
The body of Michael Myers
已在一次午夜游行中被处置
was disposed of in a midnight procession.
没有任何的墓碑和纪念碑
There would be no tombstone, no memorial.
所有的谜已经解开
The mysteries were put to bed,
我们讲述的故事也将消逝在时间之中
and the story as we told it was to fade with time.
你对科里的怀疑是对的
You were right about Corey.
我知道是他杀了那些人
I know he killed those people.
他被邪恶吞噬了
He was consumed by evil.
哈顿菲尔德的事件
The events of Haddonfield
曾带来了如此多的暴力和鲜血
that created so much violence and bloodshed
现在终于结束了
finally had resolve.
报告中确当 迈克尔·迈尔斯
Reports now confirm that Michael Myers
是在一起袭击未遂的事件中被反杀的
has indeed been killed dead after an attempted assault
被袭击对象是哈登菲尔德居民劳里·斯特罗德
of Haddonfield resident Laurie Strode.
一个奇迹般的生存故事
What an incredible story of survival
在我们的社区经历了几十年的动荡后
through decades of disturbances in our local community.
终于…
Finally...
新的开始就在眼前
New beginnings lay ahead.
我们都禁受了恐惧
Fear moves through all of us,
但我们可以自己决定 何时投降
and we decide when to surrender.
我已经与自己的恶魔人告别
I've said goodbye to my boogeyman,
但邪恶永远不会消亡
but the truth is evil doesn't die.
只是以另一种形式出现
It changes shape.
我希望你知道 我一直想着你
I wanted you to know I was thinking about you.
我想感谢你的壮举
I want to thank you for what you did.
送给你的
Enjoy.
再给我讲讲你之前说的樱花的故事吧
What was it you were saying about those cherry blossoms?